Goodbye, boss.
再见，老板。
See you tomorrow.
明天见。
I'm leaving first, brother.
我先走了，兄弟。
goodbye.
再见。
Mr. and Mrs.
先生和夫人。
Auntie is back.
阿姨回来了。
Why did you come suddenly?
你怎么突然来了
Isn't this
这不是吗
my colleagues
我的同事们
give me one
给我一个
I don't smoke.
我不抽烟。
I brought it to you.
我给你带来的。
Last year the doctor told me
去年医生告诉我
Quit smoking and drinking.
戒烟、戒酒。
I've been using it for a few months
我已经用了几个月了
no more smoking
不再吸烟
That's good
那就好
You are not a fishing law enforcement officer
你不是钓鱼执法
Is it right to test me?
考验我对吗？
I did not mean that
我不是那个意思
But honestly
但老实说
Quitting smoking is not easy.
戒烟并不容易。
You must survive.
你必须生存。
Are you still quitting candy?
你还戒烟糖果吗？
I bought you more.
我给你买了更多。
more
多一点
Huang Zicheng bought so many for me
黄子成给我买了这么多
I haven't eaten much lately
最近我没吃多少东西
No purchase required.
无需购买。
You haven't eaten yet?
你还没吃饭吧？
I definitely haven’t eaten it yet.
肯定还没吃过。
I shouldn't ask
我不应该问
I'll cook for you
我去给你做饭
Noodles are pretty good
面条还不错
Oh yes.
哦是的。
In that white porcelain jar
在那白瓷罐里
It’s this year’s new tea.
是今年的新茶。
Mix it yourself.
你自己混合一下。
OK
好的。
What is the word?
词是什么？
I'll invite you out to dinner.
我请你出去吃饭。
I found a new restaurant.
我找到了一家新餐馆。
good.
不错。
next time
下次
Wait for Zicheng to come back
等子澄回来
let's go together
我们一起去
you can also.
你也可以。
Fried noodles.
炸酱面。
OK
好的。
People have already arranged it.
人已经安排好了。
5.30pm.
下午 5.30。
In the town square,
在城镇广场上，
[In the town square. ]
[在城镇广场。]
Can he recognize me?
他能认出我吗？
He only knows things, not people.
他只认识事物，不认识人。
OK
好的。
5.30pm.
下午 5.30。
In the town square.
在城镇广场。
I doubt him
我怀疑他
There is important information about biological companies.
有关于生物公司的重要信息。
Biological groups?
生物群体？
of.
的。
Shi Tou, gambar.
Shi Tou, gambar.
The target has emerged.
目标已经出现。
understand.
理解。
The target entered the milk tea shop.
目标进入了奶茶店。
Enter your payment code here.
在此输入付款代码。
OK
好的。
How are you? This is a receipt for you.
你好吗，这是给你的小票
Thanks.
谢谢。
Hello.
你好。
give me a cup of black tea
给我一杯红茶
OK
好的。
Hello, please scan the QR code to pay.
您好，请扫码支付。
Parson is here.
帕森来了。
Hello.
你好。
Hello, I would like a glass of orange juice.
你好，我想要一杯橙汁。
Another cake.
另一个蛋糕。
wrap.
裹。
OK
好的。
Hello, please scan the QR code to pay.
您好，请扫码支付。
attention.
注意力。
A new stranger.
一个新的陌生人。
Director Qin.
秦司长。
The connection target has been determined.
连接目标已确定。
But the circumstances surrounding the transfer of the goods are unclear.
但关于货物转移的情况尚不清楚。
We have to pay attention to who is coming.
我们必须注意即将到来的人。
After leaving the market,
离开市场后，
After leaving the market.
离开市场后。
Don't lose him.
不要失去他。
Where is the courier?
快递在哪里？
If so, the sender will not move first
如果是这样，发送者不会先移动
Just pay attention.
只要注意即可。
understand.
理解。
Someone is following you.
有人在跟踪你。
Enter the mall.
进入商场。
You have become a target.
你已成为目标。
WHO？
WHO？
For example, the National Security Agency.
例如国家安全局。
The goods must not fall into Guo An's hands.
货绝对不能落到郭安的手里。
Target lost.
目标丢失。
sun
太阳
The sender suddenly disappeared.
发信人突然消失了。
Pay attention to the recipient.
注意收件人。
The goods are in his hands
货物在他手里
I doubt they've noticed
我怀疑他们已经注意到了
The consignee is ready to go out.
收货人准备出门。
Ada Guo An.
Ada Guo An.
where to.
去那里。
The item is missing.
该物品丢失。
Jiang.
蒋.
Supervise consignees.
监督收货人。
why you again
为什么又是你
Let me go.
让我走。
Everyone across the country is safe.
全国各地的每个人都很安全。
You can't go out anymore.
你不能再出去了。
I must go.
我必须去。
if not,
如果不，
complete you
完成你
You can't leave here with your stuff.
你不能带着东西离开这里。
Just change your clothes and leave.
换好衣服就走。
Give me that thing.
把那个东西给我。
There's no use them arresting you.
他们抓你是没有用的。
They'll see you soon.
他们很快就会见到你。
Time is running out.
没时间了。
Where is that thing?
那东西在哪里？
you are right.
你是对的。
The item is missing.
该物品丢失。
It's no use for them to catch me.
他们抓我是没有用的。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
before i know
在我知道之前
who betrayed me
谁背叛了我
It's possible for anyone
任何人都有可能
Go north.
向北走。
Where are the people?
人在哪里？
Already published
已经发布了
Where is this item?
该物品在哪里？
It was ruined.
它被毁了。
Gao Ke
Gao Ke
The recipient of the shipment has been controlled.
货物的收件人已被控制。
Well, I'll go now
嗯，我现在就去
Do you see what's inside?
你看到里面的东西了吗？
It should be a sample.
应该是一个样本。
In biological companies,
在生物公司中，
There are indeed nails.
确实有钉子。
You let him go on purpose again.
你又故意让他走。
catch him.
抓住他。
He won't tell anyone.
他不会告诉任何人。
He still doesn't believe you.
他还是不相信你。
Not that easy.
没那么容易。
How to make a head start
怎样头张
See us?
见到我们？
I guess
我猜测
beside him
在他身边
spy
间谍
This is our negligence
这是我们的疏忽
How was it exposed?
怎么暴露的？
have no idea.
不知道。
your identity
您的身份
Only Gao Tian knows
只有高天知道
he let me go
他让我走
Where are the samples?
样品呢？
It was ruined.
它被毁了。
sample.
样本。
Don't fall into Guo An's hands.
别落到郭安手里。
Now, he's your ace.
现在，他是你的王牌。
You must protect him.
你必须保护他。
I know.
我知道。
Bassoon.
巴松.
He is a sailor.
他是一名水手。
Code car driver.
代码汽车司机。
Responsible for sending information.
负责发送信息。
but he doesn't know
但他不知道
About Jin Hai’s condition.
关于金海的病情。
He is just a courier
他只是一名快递员
Our goal
我们的目标
It's a big hidden fish
是一条隐藏的大鱼
In Bio Group.
在生物集团。
I warned you.
我警告过你。
Stop looking for trouble.
不要再寻找麻烦了。
Someone doubted me.
有人怀疑我。
Your female colleague?
你的女同事？
before you act,
在你行动之前，
You'd better tell me first.
你最好先告诉我。
I can't save you every time.
我不能每次都救你。
Go to the department head.
去部门长吧。
Why do I think so?
我为什么这么认为？
look
你看
every move of mine
我的每一个动作
Because you have a problem,
因为你有问题，
I'm going to be in trouble.
我会遇到麻烦的。
That's fine if you think so.
你这么想就好了。
Asking questions, this time it’s the National Security Bureau
问问题，这次是国安局
How do you know we've met?
你怎么知道我们见过面？
we got the message
我们得到了信息
car driver
汽车司机
Yakabus members enter the country.
Yakabus 成员入境。
I suspect he's here to get information.
我怀疑他是来获取情报的。
We've been watching him for a long time.
我们已经观察他很长时间了。
I didn't realize you were the one who sent the message.
我没想到你就是发送信息的人。
I can not
我不能
I can't find a weakness.
我找不到弱点。
Since Yaoqie doesn’t trust me,
既然瑶切不信任我，
You don’t have to look for me anymore
你不用再找我了
They can't find you.
他们找不到你。
Can I?
我可以吗？
I want to believe you.
我愿意相信你。
What about the man you trust?
那你信任的男人呢？
Do you want me to cook for you?
你要我给你做饭吗？
You helped me today.
今天你帮了我。
I haven't thanked you yet.
我还没有感谢你呢。
at your side,
在你身边，
bukan Xiao Yi saja, kan?
bukan Xiao Yi saja, kan?
certainly.
当然。
But I'm not as good as you.
但我没有你那么好。
sorry.
对不起。
I don't like sharing with others
我不喜欢与别人分享
Another girl
又换个女孩子
You don't gossip
你不八卦
This is a sponsor
这是赞助商
I'm here to buy
我是来买的
The material in Crow's hand.
乌鸦手中的材料。
I asked him out
我约他出去
ask him out
约他出去
he gave it to me
他给了我
He gave it to me.
他把它给了我。
This is this time
这是这个时候
Boss, be generous.
老板，大方。
Wu Senlin
吴森林
people with background
有背景的人
please sign in.
请登录。
Gentlemen.
先生们。
Please come up.
请上去。
The materials in Crow's hands are quite popular.
乌鸦手中的材料，颇为吃香。
Sources say a buyer has been found.
消息称已经找到买家。
if not for
如果不是因为
owe me a favor
欠我一个人情
he won't face me
他不会面对我
Found a buyer.
找到买家了。
of.
的。
It is understood that he has already paid the deposit.
据了解，他已经支付了定金。
He's inside.
他在里面。
speak slowly
慢慢地说
sit down.
坐下。
that's right.
这是正确的。
Someone paid a deposit
有人付了押金
Want to chat more?
想多聊聊吗？
yes?
是？
Two days ago,
前两天，
Looks like what's in your hand
看起来就像你手里的东西
it's not easy
这并不容易
certainly.
当然。
If we offer a higher price,
如果我们提供更高的价格，
Can we
我们可以吗
No matter how high the price is, it can’t be sold.
卖多高也卖不出去
This is the rule.
这是规则。
Please next time
请下次
We had the opportunity to work together.
我们有机会一起工作。
OK
好的。
I also want to search
我也想搜索
stable buyer
稳定买家
It's easy and safe.
这既简单又安全。
of.
的。
But how can I be sure
但我怎么能确定
Materials in your hand
你手中的材料
Only sell to me.
只卖给我。
I said,
我说，
Business activities must abide by the rules.
经营活动必须遵守规则。
If not later
如果不晚点的话
Neither will anyone else
其他人也不会
Buy something from me.
找我买东西。
In the world of agents
在代理人的世界里
There are no rules.
没有什么规则可言。
Offline transactions
线下交易
Eliminate face-to-face copying
消除面对面复印
is the safest.
是最安全的。
impossible.
不可能的。
i won't see you
我不会见到你
agent game
代理游戏
It is the safest trading market
是最安全的交易市场
If you don't accept it,
如果你不接受，
We can no longer work together.
我们不能再一起工作了。
Be your buyer this time
这次成为你的买家
Do you accept online transactions?
接受网上交易吗？
certainly.
当然。
who is he?
他是谁？
Is he a philosophy student?
他是读哲学的人吗？
This has nothing to do with you.
这与你无关。
If he is a person who studies philosophy,
如果他是一个读哲学的人，
your transaction
您的交易
It won't be that easy.
不会那么容易。
He will cause you trouble.
他会给你带来麻烦。
Have a question for me?
找我有问题吗？
He might find you.
他可能会找到你。
Do you know where I am?
你知道我在哪里吗？
Have you read Jae-chul
你读过Jae-chul
who are you?
你到底是谁？
I'm here for
我来是为了
with you
与你
but i care more
但我更在乎
your safety
你的安全
You are not here to trade.
你不是来交易的。
do not waste time.
不要浪费时间。
How can you be sure?
你怎么确定？
He reads Jae Cheol's works
他读Jae Cheol的作品
I wasn't sure before this
在此之前我还不确定
But his earlier response
但他早些时候的回应
In principle it is certain.
原则上是可以确定的。
He can still go out now
他现在还能出去
significance
意义
He is safe for now.
他暂时还是安全的。
We can find Jae-chul reading a book
我们可以发现Jae-chul正在读书
Even the Nightmist can do it.
就连夜雾人也可以。
So his current situation
那么他现在的处境
very dangerous.
非常危险。
We must find him immediately.
我们必须立即找到他。
Many people are reading philosophy books.
很多人都在看哲学书。
How to find it?
如何找到它？
I heard your conversation didn't go well.
听说你们的谈话不顺利
what did he say?
他说什么？
He said you were insincere
他说你不真诚
and wanted to deceive him
并想欺骗他
no
不是
Tauke Wu
Tauke Wu
Want to deal with him offline
想离线和他打交道
he doesn't agree
他不同意
this game
这个游戏
Who wants to reveal something?
谁想透露一下？
one's true identity
自己的真实身份
after all,
毕竟，
He still lives with leaks
他仍然生活在漏水之中
I found you
我找到你们了
quite profitable
相当有利可图
When did you recommend me?
你什么时候推荐我的？
Are you still going to your hacker league?
还去你们的黑客联盟？
It's enough.
已经足够。
Be careful the police will find you.
小心警察会找到你的。
Oh yes.
哦是的。
Usually, he works for the same company.
通常，他在同一家公司工作。
How long does he work?
他工作多长时间？
The time is short, one or two years.
时间很短，一两年。
If it is slow, it may take more than three years.
如果慢的话，可能需要三年以上。
See when he
看看他什么时候
Get the material he wants.
得到他想要的材料。
OK
好的
Me too
我也算
Offend your friends.
冒犯你的朋友。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Decide to start a business
决定创业
There is no separation.
没有分开。
I like this girl.
我喜欢这个女孩。
How do you know I'm a girl?
你怎么知道我是女孩？
we are best friends.
我们是最好的朋友。
You hate it.
你讨厌它。
she's just a girl
她只是一个女孩
Thanks.
谢谢。
I'll call you next time.
下次我会打电话给你。
OK
好的。
Come on, miss.
来吧，小姐。
I know how to investigate.
我知道如何调查。
Speech.
讲话。
look.
看。
He got important information
他获得了重要情报
and find a buyer.
并找到买家。
The next step is
下一步是
Resign and get out of here.
辞职离开这里。
your previous question
你之前的问题
It must be interesting
一定很有趣
his attention.
他的注意力。
He will go faster.
他会走得更快。
make sense.
说得通。
I think
我觉得
we can try
我们可以尝试
Ask Yaoyao for help.
向瑶瑶求助。
Yao Yao
Yao Yao
he is reading
他在读书
Ask him to help investigate this person
叫他帮忙调查这个人
No, Yaoyao can't.
不能，瑶瑶不能。
His status is not suitable for intervention
他的身份不适合干预
We suspect someone
我们怀疑有人
There is night fog.
有夜雾。
our investigation
我们的调查
It must be done in secret.
必须秘密进行。
How do we investigate?
我们如何调查？
hunter.
猎人。
Hunting companies dominate
狩猎公司占主导地位
All resignation information
所有辞职信息
and information about employees who are resigning.
以及有关即将辞职的员工的信息。
we can pass
我们可以通过
through this channel
通过这个渠道
Awesome, Sister Xi
厉害了夕姐
give it to me.
把它给我。
I know people from hunting companies.
我认识狩猎公司的人。
Why does everyone know each other?
为什么大家都认识？
when i graduate,
当我毕业时，
With my excellent experience,
凭借我出色的经验，
[My resume is outstanding. ]
[我的简历非常出色。]
invite
邀请
Finally I refused.
最后我拒绝了。
Don't you want to be blacklisted?
你不想被列入黑名单吗？
Don't worry.
不用担心。
not like this.
不是这样的。
split in trade
贸易中的分裂
We also have people in our hunting company
我们狩猎公司也有人
If you are so proactive
如果你这么主动的话
I can only suspect that you have other motives.
我只能怀疑你另有目的。
I do this to...
我这样做是为了...
For national security.
为了国家安全。
You do this for someone.
你为某人这样做。
small.
小的。
If you think of it this way, the pattern is very small.
如果你这样想的话，图案就会很小。
I go first, you run
我先走，你跑
Don't run away, bye.
别逃了，再见。
I left the keys at home.
我把钥匙留在家里了。
I will go to your house.
我会去你家。
My house is a mess. Only next time.
我的房子很乱。只能下次了。
You are looking for an important company.
您正在寻找一家重要的公司。
My car is here, I'm leaving first.
我的车来了，我先走了。
Why can't we leave after we break up?
散了怎么走不了？
Geshe
格西
from hunter
来自猎人
Latest information received
已收到最新信息
Newest
最新的
include
包括
who is ready to resign
谁准备辞职
and intends to resign
并打算辞职
and their resume.
和他们的简历
Also inside.
也在里面。
I sent you an email.
我给你发了一封邮件。
Thanks.
谢谢。
The job is done.
工作完成了。
wake up.
醒来。
Can't sleep well
睡不好
I don't go to bed until four o'clock
我四点钟才去睡觉
I changed my bag again today
今天又换包了
Is this beautiful?
这漂亮吗？
limited edition
限量版
I don't want to buy it.
我不想买。
I will regret it for a year.
我会后悔一年。
During this year,
在这一年里，
only a meager salary
只有微薄的薪水
I’ve bought a bag, what do you want to eat?
已经买了一袋了，想吃什么？
I eat you
我吃你
If I don't have money,
如果我没有钱，
You can't see me starving
你看不到我挨饿
Don't count on it.
不要指望。
I checked yesterday.
我昨天检查过。
Last few years,
最近几年，
some scandal
一些丑闻
on other internet platforms.
在其他互联网平台上。
some people
有些人
thereby leaking user privacy
从而泄露用户隐私
And those who fake clicks
还有那些伪造点击量的人
Who deliberately manipulates the topic.
谁故意操纵话题。
They have one thing in common.
他们有一个共同点。
There must be someone
一定有人
into them
进入他们
from a technical point of view
从技术角度来看
From a technical perspective.
从技术角度来看。
In fact, it's a scandal
事实上，这是一个丑闻
In the end the truth was not revealed.
最终没有透露真相。
Everything will end.
一切都会结束。
you think
您认为
This time our crisis
这次我们的危机
Not one thing.
不是一件事。
But done by the same group.
但由同一个小组完成。
they use the same method
他们使用相同的方法
Also used to threaten other platforms
还用来威胁其他平台
and succeeded.
并成功。
if
如果
As I expected,
正如我所预料的那样，
Then this guy
然后这个家伙
maybe once
也许曾经
In some iQiyi.
在一些爱奇艺。
continue.
继续。
I investigated Shi Qi's information.
我调查了石奇的资料。
He has worked for Company A for two years.
他在A公司工作了两年。
During this period,
在这段时期，
The company has also had its share of scandals.
这家公司也曾曝出丑闻。
According to the resume,
根据简历，
Shi Qi.
Shi Qi.
Indeed he was suspected.
确实他被怀疑了。
if it's not the first time
如果不是第一次
do something like this,
做这样的事情，
It turns out
事实证明
he made a lot of money
他赚了很多钱
through this channel
通过这个渠道
so
所以
his financial status
他的经济状况
Absolutely good
绝对不错
But look, Principal Zhou
但是周校长你看
him on the address page
地址页上的他
Full of ordinary neighborhoods.
充满了普通的社区。
Although I have never been to his house
虽然我没去过他家
But I searched online.
但我在网上搜索过。
The area is quite remote
该地区相当偏僻
The rent is also cheap.
房租也便宜。
After all, he is not rich
毕竟他并不富有
He is not a rich man.
他不是一个富人。
Could it be him
难道是他
deliberately hidden
故意隐藏
own money
自己的钱
Who are you
你是
The son of the invisible millionaire
隐形富翁的儿子
There is a mine at home.
家里有矿。
I admit
我承认
imitate
模仿
is that true
是真的吗
This work is quite good
这个作品相当不错
Yes, I think so too.
是的，我也这么认为。
Can't see this
这个看不到
Later you refused to give me this land
后来你拒绝了这片土地给我
Yes.
是的。
no problem
没问题
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
He always buys luxury goods.
他总是买奢侈品。
But he told me,
但他告诉我，
all fake.
都是假的。
The conversation still needs to be discussed.
谈话仍需讨论。
But I think,
但我觉得，
You can continue to investigate
你可以继续调查
Continue to investigate
继续调查
if necessary
如果需要的话
Use a little trick.
使用一点方法。
For example
例如
For example, record a conversation
例如，记录对话
Or the reality of his family.
或者他家庭的真实情况。
this...
这...
You are a friend.
你是朋友。
It doesn't seem difficult to you.
对你来说似乎并不困难。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
I know you.
我认识你们。
Don't you want to know?
你不想知道吗？
what friends do you have
你有哪些朋友
for you?
给你？
OK
好的。
Let me try.
让我尝试。
Why?
为什么？
I want to change my job.
我想换工作。
Why suddenly?
为什么突然？
what happen?
发生什么事？
It has been a long time.
已经很久了。
The hunter dug me out.
猎人把我挖了出来。
My heart was pounding.
我的心砰砰直跳。
Which company do you want to go to?
你想去哪家公司？
Three major game companies
三大游戏公司
I have not decided yet.
我还没想好。
Have you mentioned it to the staff?
你有跟工作人员提过吗？
of.
的。
No, you've thought about it
不，你已经考虑过了
you make a decision
你做出决定
Just leave me like this?
就这样离开我吗？
You want to go to your boss
你想去老板身边
I'm bored living here.
我住在这里很无聊。
But some of these companies
但其中一些公司
Everything is nearby.
一切都在附近。
We can play together again.
我们又可以一起玩了。
Si Qi.
Si Qi.
Let's sign autographs.
我们来签名吧。
Geshe
格西
between them,
它们之间，
i know someone
我认识一个人
Zhou Si Qi?
Zhou Si Qi?
of.
的。
He is Yaoyao's best friend.
他是瑶瑶最好的朋友。
I've investigated
我调查过
his past
他之前的过去
you don't speak
你不说话
Very similar indeed
确实很相似
We've checked.
我们已经查过了。
The best person for Crow's situation.
最适合乌鸦处境的人
So does he.
他也是。
but...
但...
He is not a crow.
他不是乌鸦。
why is it impossible
为什么不可能
Jiang Xiaohua reminded me
姜小花提醒我了
hacker
黑客
Can be disguised
可以伪装
own identity.
自己的身份。
I was surprised he was a crow.
我很惊讶他是一只乌鸦。
Have you had any contact with him?
你和他有接触过吗？
No.
不。
But isn't he?
但他不是吗？
Yaoyao's best friend?
瑶瑶最好的朋友？
Before that, I always heard Yao Ming mention him.
在此之前，我总听姚明提起他。
you say
你说
Yaoyao's identity, he
瑶瑶的身份，他
Why is it so complicated?
为什么这么复杂？
OK
好的。
We'll take care of the rest.
我们会处理剩下的事情。
What should I do next?
接下来我应该做什么？
continue working.
继续工作。
If anything happens I will contact you.
如果有什么事我会联系你。
Are you leaving me again?
你又要离开我了吗？
of course not
当然不是
your abilities in the game
你在游戏中的能力
Really helped us.
真的帮助了我们。
Geshe
格西
You are more loyal than Gao Tianyang.
你比高天阳还忠诚。
I'll tell him on your behalf.
我会代表你告诉他。
goodbye.
再见。
Shi Qi will resign.
石奇将辞职。
I know.
我知道。
This is no coincidence, right?
这不是巧合，对吧？
The goal has been achieved.
目标已经达到了。
Definitely need to be ready to go.
绝对需要做好出发的准备。
I've looked into it.
我调查过。
his bag
他的包
it is true.
是真的。
It seems that he deliberately concealed it
看来他是故意隐瞒的
own financial ability.
自己的经济能力。
Now it seems
现在看来
Mr. Zhou, you are right
周总，你说得对
I might
我可能
don't understand him
不明白他
his address
他的地址
is fake.
是假的。
please let me investigate
请让我调查一下
where does he live
他住在哪里
OK
好的。
Look for opportunities.
寻找机会。
I'll go see it with him
我和他一起去看看
Don't let him notice.
别让他注意到。
Be careful.
当心。
if there is nothing
如果什么都没有的话
I go first.
我先走了。
Go to work.
去工作。
I found someone who asked me to investigate.
我找到了一个叫我去调查的人。
soon
很快
Yaoyao is very smart
瑶瑶很聪明
You just sent it to him
你刚刚发给他
In order to attract Huang Zicheng,
为了吸引黄子成，
it's useless
没用的
useless
无用
Neither can Mr. Yu
于先生也不会
at your place
在你的地方
but a smart man
但一个聪明人
Usually not very obedient.
平时不太听话。
I will educate him well.
我会好好教育他的。
Bagi Zhou Si Qi,
Bagi Zhou Si Qi,
Please take care of me, Boss Zhang.
请张老板多多关照。
take it out
把它拿出来
In his hands.
在他手里。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'll take care of it.
我会照顾它。
That's very good.
那挺好的。
You repeat what he said.
你重复他的话。
useless
无用
Neither can Mr. Yu
于先生也不会
at your place
在你的地方
but a smart man
但一个聪明人
Usually not very obedient.
平时不太听话。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'll take care of it.
我会照顾它。
Just to name a few such poems
仅举几句这样的诗句
of.
的。
So incomplete.
太不完整了。